This love in my heart,
it will burn on forever!
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop!
No matter where you
are, nothing is too far!
With our everlasting bones,
we'll reach it, we are home!
I'm
so truly grateful!
I ran into you on that day so long ago!
We laughed every moment
with tears in our eyes!
Till we knew we weren't alone!
The blowing wind came in
and joined us on our way!
And with it I know we'll rise!
We'll be flying up high!
Why, tell me why are you giving up?
Why, tell me why you want to fight alone?
Hey, what kind of future
do you think you have?
Your dream is already in your hands.
This love in my heart,
it will burn off forever.
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
I don't matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting plans,
we'll reach it, we are home.
From the horizon, out on
the edge of the world.
If there is a place that
I'd want to take you to.
Let's head for it then!
But as for the way we already know.
We promised it long ago.
You scream by your voice.
That can't break through the silence.
Feeling defeated.
It crushes your helpless heart.
I've got your back, I swear.
I'll always be here.
Let's put our fate within
this light under the sun.
Can you close your eyes and
just listen to my voice?
Let's find the answer together.
I'm telling you in our path.
I trust that it will lead us.
To another sea untarded.
Cause now we are home.
On the horizon, out on
the edge of the world.
There is a place that
I want to take you to.
Let's head forth and.
But as for the way, we already know.
We promised it long ago.
Great work, Ichigi.
And Niji, well done.
you could say the war-torn brock collie
is just another victim of the fall of
the doflamingo regime once their army
could no longer source
weapons from him they
sought our military strength for assistance
suppressing the enemy only got them so
far half-hearted sympathy simply leads to
more bloodshed such a
pity who gives a crap
about their reasons whoever ponies up the
most money gets the win it's that simple
we couldn't play both sides in secret and
easily earn twice as much you know that's
something a pirate would
do let us not forget
our nation is still a member of the world
government speaking of
which dad the reverie
is just around the corner that's correct
However, I suspect that they will likely
strip us of our right to attend this year.
Bear this in mind, though.
The power we'll be gaining
is going to be tremendous.
Germa will be forever changed.
It's rare for something to
bring Dad this much pleasure.
You really should be honored.
Who'd have predicted you'd
come in handy one day?
You listening?
It really took us by surprise
when you ran away from home.
But we never forgot.
Your name would come up from time to time.
We all had our own speculations about you.
Oh, you'll love this.
We all assumed you were dead.
We even played a game where we'd come up
with all the funny ways
you might have died.
There's still food on your plate.
Don't waste it, Niji.
Huh, this, yeah. I'm done.
Not hungry.
I filled up on a ton of chocolate earlier.
Besides this thick sauce looks disgusting.
You see how gooey and nasty it is?
It's going straight to the trash.
Finish it.
You don't know the value of food or
how much effort goes into cooking.
You stuck up, Prince!
Shut the hell up!
You weakling.
Watch who you're speaking to.
You have no right to insult me like that.
Call the head, chef.
Bring me Cosette.
This vile-looking slop you dared serve
us caused my brother to upset me! Sorry.
I deeply apologize, sir.
I never should have offered a
dish so appalling to you. Enough.
Now don't you move an inch, Cosette.
You low-life bastard, how could you?
Are you trying to leave
a scar on a lady's face?
Huh?
A lady?
How stupid are you?
You're really going to go to bed
for a glorified kitchen wench?
What a gentleman now there's
food all over the floor!
It's called aligo and
it's made from cheese.
Blended into mashed potatoes,
master sanji, please!
I'll clean it.
Potatoes strengthen your immune.
system.
Plus, they stabilize blood pressure.
They're very nutritious.
I assume, due to your
noble status, this fine confit was
carefully selected and prepared.
It's an awfully elaborate
dish to make for breakfast. Hmm?
Don't mess her, Sanji.
Royal blood must never eat off the floor.
Yeah, whoa.
Have you lost your damn mind?
That's vile the flavor is impeccable
Poverty's done a number on you Sanji
I appreciate it, sir.
You are a blemish on the Ventsmoke name.
I know this is beyond your comprehension,
but I'm embarrassed to be related to you.
Oh, yeah?
Disrespecting such fine food is one thing,
but raising your hand to a woman is sick.
Just because you're born into royalty
doesn't mean you can treat her like dirt.
Everything you guys represent
goes against my principles.
Oh, Sanji, your head is poisoned by
the blustering ideology of the weak.
Ever since we were children, your
thinking has been incomprehensible.
Royalty abides by its own set of rules.
You're the one out of touch here.
Your brothers are right.
You have no idea how
the world truly works.
Could it be that your misguided
mind was corrupted by this man?
Big Mom's network of information
collectors is impressive.
I understand that around two years
ago you worked in his restaurant.
We've uncovered the location.
A seafaring eatery called the Baratier.
I believe this is a
recent photo, is it not?
Is something wrong?
You're turning as white as a ghost, boy.
Where'd all that chivalry go, Sanji?
Say something, huh?
Hey!
And those are?
A preventative measure for
an unexpected bon voyage.
We can expect both
Swahed and Monsieur Sanji
himself to attempt la
résistance for la mariage.
To ensure it is seen all the way through,
you may have the bracelet along
with the knowledge of his weakness.
That's his weakness?
In other words, this is only a safety
measure in the event you refuse to comply.
Needless to say,
I won't hesitate to relieve this man
of his head if push comes to shove.
I wouldn't do anything
drastic if I were you.
You should know what we're capable of.
Don't resist.
Forget your friends and accept
your marriage to pudding quietly.
Do that, and everything
will work out just fine.
What happened?
You're missing a leg.
That's correct.
Why'd you help me?
Old fool.
It doesn't make sense to sacrifice
so much for me, so why tell me why?
Well, it's simple.
For my entire life, I've
had the same dream as you.
Sea all blue.
Tang, you old fart!
You really did it!
This is the Sea Restaurant!
Are you ready?
Cause we're gonna be busy.
We'll be just fine!
Cause you got me!
Pay attention, brat.
You're moving too slow, brat.
No, I'm not, old man.
Stop fooling around with
the ladies, you brat.
Be quiet, brat.
Stop it, you brat.
You little brat. Little brat.
Hey, brat.
You little brat.
Hey, Sanji.
Take care.
Don't catch cold.
Get to the chef!
You old geezer!
I can't thank you enough
for all you've done!
I won't forget your kindness!
I owe my life to you!
Let's have a peaceful
wedding ceremony tomorrow.
We'll be having lunch today with Big
Mom and Pudding, so go get ready.
We'll head over to her castle shortly.
Any objections, Sanji?
Where's that damn straw
hat hiding the hunt is on
Just ten minutes gotta recharge.
I can't even use Haki yet
Is somebody there
Hey, help!
Someone call a doctor!
Come on, stay with me!
Those bastards, they waited
until I wasn't around.
There's nothing she could
have done to deserve this.
They beat a woman unconscious!
Unbelievable!
I've never met a bigger scumbag!
This is all your fault, Sanji.
Why is that?
You gave that homely commoner
a taste of self-confidence.
What do you mean by that, asshole?
Why don't you go and take that up with Niji,
considering he's the guilty party here.
Come on, I'll take you to him now.
Don't you worry, it's gonna be okay, hmm.
You coming?
Let's go already.
Yeah, can't wait to settle this!
What is this place?
You wouldn't remember.
You ran away before any of us
were old enough to come down here.
54 units of Type M-B,
30 units of Type M-ST,
and 21 of Type M-H need restocks. Noted.
What the hell am I looking at?
A beautiful sight to behold.
The reason why Germa is
feared around the world.
Say hello to our famous soldiers!
General Cracker!
That can't be!
The same Cracker?
So, humor me, King Bowne.
Want to explain why in the hell
you're helping the Straw Hats?
Velocita, it's a very good reason.
On second, Dot, never mind.
I'll just kill you all instead.
This guy's scary.
Are you surprised?
I'm the Sweet Three General Cracker.
Don't you touch her!
Nami's part of my crew!
It's Straw Hat!
Germa double six soldiers?
How's that possible?
Why are they in water?
It's bioculture fluid.
They all have the same face.
Are they actually alive?
Sanji, human beings, can be constructed.
did.
We've been a nation of
science for generations.
He may not look it, but
our old man is a renowned
scientist, you know.
Got started long before we were born.
He used to be a part of a foreign research
team operating outside of the law,
exploring and developing weaponry with the
infamous Dr. Vegapunk.
He worked alongside that guy?
In his younger days, yeah. Back then,
vegapunk's breakthrough
discovery was the presence
of bloodline elements
within living things.
He essentially discovered the
blueprints of life and that's
bound to ruffle some feathers
playing god and all that,
so when the world government caught
wind of things they arrested vegapunk.
The research team was disbanded or rather
it was absorbed into
the government however.
However, Dad was able
to evade their reach,
and secretly continue his
studies here in Germa.
That research being...
duplicating and augmenting a life.
That's the very reason this
underground facility was built.
All the soldiers here are synthetic
duplicates of a select few superior fighters.
They're clones, soldiers!
They're clones?
they're blissfully
unaware of that of course
it's funny
nations all over the world
fear our soldiers but they
also wish they had some of
their own they envy our strength
what's more our men are as
obedient as they are strong they're
programmed not to fear death
or ever turn on their masters
if they die we can just replace
them it only takes five years to
create a new 20 year old fighter
you're looking at our soldier storage
depot check out this guy technically
five years old but ready for war
he doesn't even realize what he's
being robbed of stop it that's enough
This makes me sick!
Sanji!
Back when we received word
that you would become a pirate,
We thought maybe the little failure might
have gotten his feet
wet and grown up some.
But it turns out you're still a disaster.
Niji.
You sick bastard.
Why aren't you working?
We got a big head now, don't we?
What's the matter with you?
You'll treat her like that!
You attacked a girl, a cute girl, so
now you're gonna pay back off, Sanji!
Remember, we're still.
holding a certain somebody
hostage in the East Blue.
Time for stealth.
Are you mad?
Oh, come on.
Do you actually like that
little cooking wench?
Don't fight back.
Make one wrong move, and someone will die.
Henry Needle!
Oh, why didn't you tell me?
If I knew you liked her, I
wouldn't have messed up her face.
But oh well, too late now, I guess.
Yeah, kind of a shame.
Well, if the busted-up
face isn't a deal-breaker,
then maybe I can make her
your personal attendant.
Look at all of us, together again.
Sanji, you're one of us now.
Actually, on that note, I think we should
re-establish the hierarchy around here.
As you know, you are a worthless failure.
Children, of all the things I've
built, you are the greatest.
You're an incredible team of
scientifically modified superhumans.
Humans, the fruits of my extensive
research—brilliance, unlike normal humans!
You are unbound by emotion;
soon you'll command military
forces of your own and one
day lead Germa Double Six
toward even greater heights!
All thanks to the power of
science I gave you—the power!
Your job is to train.
to train
Sanji, it's your turn to go!
Ha, ha, ha!
Ah!
Ow, ow, ow, it burns!
Where's Sanji, who died?
I don't know.
Come here, little guy.
I'm not going to hurt you.
What do you keep playing
with that dumb turtle for?
Why did you do that? You did!
Don't touch me!
There!
That should teach you.
No, it really hurts!
Hey, I can both!
Please stop me!
I feel low, DG!
Hey, the fight's over!
Hey, let go!
I'm not done yet!
Why is Sanji so weak?
The gap in their scores keeps increasing.
We got the test results back, sir.
Ichiji, Niji, and Yonji are making
excellent progress in their training.
Their exoskeletons have developed and
according to the data we've gathered,
their flexibility and strength are
already equivalent to those of grown men.
On the other hand, it pains me
to tell you, but Yon Sanji is.
Go on. Say it.
Unfortunately, he's proven
himself to be a failure.
We were certain that we
had successfully modified
the bloodline elements
for each of the children.
But for some unknown reason,
Sanji seemed to have converted back
to their original configuration.
That must mean...
Sanji's normal.
He's just human.
There.
Thank you, but why'd you help? What?
You'd rather I didn't?
Mm-mm-mm.
I'm glad you do. You're nice.
Nuh-uh. Shut up.
When they're mean, you
laugh also. How come?
It's not like I have a choice.
If I try to stop them, then
they'll just start picking on me.
No thanks.
Oh, he's here.
Go ahead, eat.
I made it for you.
Hope you like it.
Well?
Sanji!
Ah, you're cooking for the
rats again, aren't you?
I thought I told you royalty
doesn't serve anyone.
But I just am.
She's dead, and you know that.
So stop trying to be like your mother.
Unlike your siblings, you were
born without an ounce of talent.
So you'll train. Hard.
A hundred times harder than them.
You're my son,
which means you're an integral part of my
plan to restore the Germa Empire's glory.
Do not disappoint me!
There.
Don't ever cook again.
Hey, Slowpoke, can't you run any faster?
Pathetic.
Nothing's changed.
He has no potential?
None.
Then it seems he's simply a waste of life.
What should we do, sir?
My poor son lost in an accident.
How tragic!
I was hoping to see the day that all five
of my children became warriors for Germa,
but sadly our precious Sanji
was taken from us far too soon.
What is this thing?
It's really heavy.
I can't take it off.
What are you guys doing to me?
Do you think Sanji's really dead?
Who cares!
We don't need that loser around.
Don't leave you.
Can't lock me up forever.
Sorry, but your father was
the one who decided this.
It is harsh, but this is not a mistake.
He intends to make it as
if you were never born.
But why?
Why did I do wrong, Dad?
Let me out.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I was forced to leave.
Please help me!
I can't live in here by myself!
Dad! No!